There's this term in the industry of diversity and inclusion when, you know, it was really kind of popular race in 2020 and companies made a lot of promises.
One of the phrases was bring your whole self to work.
Yeah.
Bring your best self to work.
Now, what you're going to have to realize is the company has a version that is defined as best or whole.
Yeah.
So you have to be in line with that.
So for example, Lisa Beasley was telling me a story of how she said, hey, this company said I can show up as my whole self.
So she would show up to these pivotal work meetings with like smoking a blunt in her mouth.
And we said, well, that's not your best self.
And she said, well, it is.
It is.
So like who's to say?
Well, the company, the company can tell you who your best self is.
So if you want to know who your best or whole self is, think about what company you're at.
See what they want your best and whole self to be and map that onto yourself.